-肯 你还好吗  -他还好吗
- Hey, Ken. Are you okay? - Is he okay?
他在卫生间里
Uh, he's in the bathroom.
欢迎 先生
Hey! Hey, sir!
飞机正在回程途中
Jet's en route back.
先生 我们要去哪儿
And, uh, where we headed, sir?
好了 飞机呢 我们能走了吗
Okay. Where are the planes? Can we go?
用不了一小时就能走了
Should be no more than an hour.
我给咱们找了一间不错的候机厅
I got us a nice room to wait in.
虽然可能也没多好
At least, not that nice, actually,
但已经是我能找到的最好的了
but it was the nicest I could source.
你们知道我们要去哪儿吗
Where are we going, do you know?
纽约吧 也许日内瓦
E...Either New York or Geneva
伦敦 新加坡 洛杉矶都有可能
or London or Singapore or L.A.
行吧 谢了
Okay. Thank you.
-他刚才说了什么  -没说什么
- What's he saying? - Not much.
那啥 有人知道他在想什么吗
Look, I mean, do we know what's he thinking?
好吧 他一直在说他妈妈的事儿
Yeah, well, he's talking about his Mom a lot.
-好吧  -什么
- Oh! Okay. - His mom?
我们有什么对策
What...what's the play?
不知道
I don't know.
涌现了很多有趣的点子
Lot of interesting ideas flying around.
我被开了 他被开了 她升职了
I got fired. He got fired. She got promoted.
我被反聘回来了 她又降级了 是吧...
I got re-hired. She got demoted, right? It's...
磨蹭什么呢
Come on!
爸 想要我跟你一路吗
Dad? Want me to ride with you?
怎么 你想给我口
You wanna suck my dick?
性侵指控铺天盖地
Is what he said to his son
他还对自己的儿子说这种话
as the sexual assault allegations poured in.
兄弟
Hey, dude.
回头打给你
Let me call you back.
肯
Hey, Ken.
你还好吗 能吭一声儿吗
If, if you're okay, will you just say, "Okay,"
这样我就能知道你还好
so that I know you're okay?
要不然... 我就得破门而入了
Because otherwise I...I'll have to break the door down
我不是太想... 我也不知道自己能不能做到
and I don't really want... I don't know if I'll be able to.
但是...
Wha... But, um...
好了 各就各位
Okay. Action stations.
我们走 准备大干一场
Let's fucking go, let's get into this.
继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 1 集
肯 我们去哪儿啊
And where are we going, Ken?
回公司 抢得先机 找好律师和公关
Waystar, plant a flag, fix on my lawyer, PRs,
动摇一些独立董事
get some independent directors shaking,
没准还要去局里喝喝茶
and maybe ride in to see the fucking Feds.
不予评论 不予评论
No comment! No comment!
-不予评论 不予评论  -你不说话就好了
- No comment! No comment! - You don't have to say that.
不一定非得说出来 格雷格 不说话就好了
You don't have to say that, Greg, just don't comment.
-请让一下 -不予评论 不予评论
- Excuse me. - No comment! No comment!
别录了 别录了
Stop! Stop! Stop it!
-好了 杰西 走吧  -好的
- Okay, Jess, let's go. - Uh-huh.
-这是公司的车  -什么
- This is a company vehicle. - What?
我是说 我并不想插足你们的争斗
I mean, I don't have a dog in this fight.
但是既然你已经公开替公司
But since you just clearly opened the company up
接受幕后调查和诉讼
to investigation, lawsuits,
我想你可能已不再是公司的一份子了
I imagine you're no longer working for the company?
不是啊 我恰恰是在为公司的利益着想
Well, no, because I was acting in the best interests of the company.
是吗 违反保密职责算吗
Yeah? Violating your duty of confidentiality?
违反了你作为董事的信托责任也算吗
Violating your fiduciary duties as a director?
听着 卡洛丽娜 我需要密不透风的作战小队 不含杂质
Look. I need a sealed unit here, Karolina. I need a clean jar.
所以... 你到底要不要为革命出力
So... so... are you in for this fucking revolution?
我当然知道这很刺激 我...
No, I know it's exciting. And, and I...I...I s...
-我...  -你是站在我这边的吧 是或不是
- I... - Are you with me, yes or no?
肯 你为什么要这么做
Why did you do it like that, Ken?
-你知情吗  -我吗 不知情
- I mean, did you know? - Me? No. No.
不知情 我没有提前接到通知 我对他的评论感到很惊讶
No, I had no prior warning and I was surprised at his comments,
但现在我十分关心这事 希望听到更多回应
but now I am obviously concerned and interested to hear more.
-好吧  -卡洛丽娜 这是你人生的分叉点
- Okay. - This is a fork in your life, Karolina.
你正在一辆开向正义的车上
This is the righteous vehicle.
-只是... 只是...  -明白了 停车
- It's just not... It's not... - Okay. Stop the car.
-下车 请下车 我要打电话了  -肯...
-Out. Out. Please. I need to make calls. - Ken...
我的汤里容不下你这颗老鼠屎 好吗
I can't have weevils in the fucking flour sack, okay?
-现在 下车  -肯
- Out. Now. - Ken?
你今天听到的一切都是要保密的
Everything you've heard today is privileged.
敢泄露给其他人 我他妈的告死你
Repeat anything and I'll sue you out of your fucking ass.
-你跟我来吗 格雷格  -我...
- Are you coming, Greg? - I...
我...
I, uh, I...
我... 我还是跟着大部队吧
I...I...I think I'm just gonna catch a ride with these guys.
-好  -行吗 谢谢你
- Right. - Okay? Thank you.
你怎么被撵下车了 怎么回事
Why'd you get kicked out of the car? What happened?
你怎么从肯德尔的车上下来了
Why did you leave Kendall's car?
他要去机场吗
Was he driving to the airport?
你有什么要说的吗
Do you have anything to say?
洛根·罗伊本人完全知晓
Logan Roy was personally and fully aware
明亮星邮轮上犯下的罪行
of the crimes committed aboard Brightstar Cruises.
肯德尔·罗伊说他父亲支付了数百万美元的封口费
Kendall Roy says his father oversaw millions of dollars of payments
用于隐藏和掩盖邮轮事故的犯罪事实
to hide and cover-up criminal activity at the cruise line.
罗伊接着对他的父亲和韦斯达·罗伊科公司的价值观和行径
Roy went on to deliver a blistering denunciation of his father and the values
韦斯达·罗伊科的
公关主管在中城被赶下车
-进行了强烈的谴责  -干得好
- and practices at Waystar Royco. -Nice.
韦斯达·罗伊科的
公关主管在中城被赶下车
整个媒体帝国和保守派新闻频道的母公司
The media empire and parent company of the conservative news channel,
泛美网络科技公司 以及记者...
ATN, and the correspondent that...
你其实是怎么想的
So, what are you actually thinking?
-我怎么想的  -对 你怎么想的
- What am I thinking? - Yeah, what are you thinking?
什么意思 就什么而言
What you mean? In terms of what?
当然是就当下的... 局势而言
Um, in terms of the fucking...the situation?
我在想 我们现在只需要支援老爸
I'm thinking that we just need to back Dad right now,
应该不会有人有别的想法吧
and I can't believe anyone would think anything else.
当然 当然不会
Yeah. Yeah, of course. Yeah.
但是呢... 我其实在想...
But... what am I actually thinking?
什么
Hmm?
好吧 我在想"他是不是嗑嗨了"
Well, I'm thinking, "Is he toast?"
我操 真的吗
Oh, fuck, you are? Really?
真的 那你是怎么想的
Yeah, well, what, what are you thinking?
我不知道
I don't know.
我在想 也许我不应该想
Yeah, I am thinking that maybe I shouldn't be thinking,
"他是不是嗑嗨了"
"Is he toast?"
他还好吗
Is he okay?
我真觉得咱们该行动了
I really think we should react.
说真的 我觉得他绝对在嗑什么
By George, I think he's on to something!
大家伙 雨果准备好飞机了
Hey, Hugo's got planes.
听着 我的电话快被打爆了
Hi. Listen, I'm drowning in calls.
我想否认那些捕风捉影的猜测
And I want to deny, you know, speculation.
所以 我只想确认一下
So, uh, I'm just checking that obviously
我个人发表以下意见
we're all good if I say, for a starter,
那就是他从没伤害过任何人...
that he never hurt anyone, and he never...
也没碰过别人 大家都没意见吧
touched anyone, personally?
你大可放心地说 雨果
You can reassure on that, Hugo.
-那就好  -你们知道吗
- Good. - Did you know?
康纳 罗曼 小西
Connor? Roman? Shiv?
你们知道吗
Did you know?
你说什么
Wh...What's that?
你们知道他要这么干吗
Did you know he was going to do that?
-我在想  -当然不知道了 爸
- I was wondering. - Well, obviously not, Dad.
好吧
Uh-huh.
肯德尔脑子有病 他疯了
Kendall's mentally ill. He's insane.
我手机呢
Where's my phone?
不知道 老爸 等我们打给你
Don't know, Pop. We'll call you.
对 你静音了吗
Uh, yeah, you got it on silent?
我想让丽莎·亚瑟做我的私人律师
Okay, I think I want Lisa Arthur as my personal lawyer,
你能给雷米打个电话 让他也找找其他人吗
but can you call Remi to hit me up with other names?
好
Uh-huh.
格雷格 我要是有什么不测
Greg, Greg, if I get taken out on other shit,
我可能需要你帮我测测文化温度
I might need you to take my cultural temperature.
-好的 了解了  -行吗
- Uh-huh. Got it. - Okay?
比如呢 那是什么意思啊
As in? Uh, wh... what does that, uh, mean?
比如在我的媒体监控到位之前
Like before I get my media monitoring in place
我可能需要你把社会政治温度计
I might need you to slide the sociopolitical thermometer
塞进这个国家的屁眼里 看看是多少度
up the nation's ass and take a reading.
行吗 我有点晕
Okay? I'll get seasick.
给我原始数据就行了
Just feed me the metadata, anything that's gonna
一切能把好评转到我头上的数据都可以 懂吗
move the market on me reputationally, yeah?
当然 当然 没问题
Uh-huh, uh-huh, yeah. Sure.
媒体监控部门就位
Uh, media monitoring department over here.
大家都在给我推荐丽莎·亚瑟
Wow, everyone is telling me Lisa Arthur.
就她了
She's my girl.
你有没有帮我找到她的资料 杰西
Did you... did you get her avails for me, Jess?
我们已经联系她了...
Um, we have a call out to her...
爸
好吧
Okay.
您好 我是肯德尔的助理杰西·乔丹
Jess Jordan on Kendall's phone.
-是他吗  -您好
- Is it him? - Hi.
-肯德尔在处理...  -听着就好了
- Kendall's, uh, just attending... - Just listen.
其他事 您有什么事情我替您转达
to some other matters but I can pass on your thoughts.
他... 他说什么
What...what's he saying?
-你想知道吗  -当然
- Do you wanna know? - Yeah.
好的 我转告他
Okay. I'll tell him.
他说 你这么做让他那边很难堪
Uh, he says that this could get very ugly for him.
你这招走得漂亮
You played a decent move.
如果你能收回自己的话
If you were to retract
然后说你状态不佳 所以说错话了
and say that you were unwell and that you misspoke,
也许还有商量的余地
then maybe there's a deal here.
这样吧 告诉他 从法律上讲 我现在和他交谈是不明智的
You know what? Tell him, legally, it's not wise for me to talk to him,
但是 我会和政府方面取得联系
but that I'm going to be in contact with the government
现在是他退位的好时机
and that this would be a good moment for him to step down.
好的 他听到了
Okay, he heard.
...我要碾碎他的骨头
...that I'm gonna grind his fucking bones
来做面包[出自童话杰克与魔豆]
to make my bread.
他说 既然这样
Uh, he says, in that case,
他就要碾碎你的骨头来做面包
he's going to grind up your bones to make his bread.
好啊
Okay?
告诉他
Well, tell him,
我一定会爬上那根狗日的豌豆茎
that I'm gonna run up off the fucking beanstalk.
好 洛根 他说 既然这样
Okay. Logan? Yeah, he says in that case
他一定会爬上那根... 豌豆茎
he's going to run up off the, uh, beanstalk?
他好像在笑 但不是那种 善意的笑
He's kind of laughing. But not, like, nice laughing.
你就说 他应该退一步 与我合作
Just tell him he should step back and cooperate.
我不想看到他进监狱
I don't want to see him behind bars.
我们可能不再站在同一阵线 但我也不想那样
We may no longer be on the same side, but I don't want that.
狗屁
That's bullshit.
道貌岸然的狗屁
That's fucking sanctimonious bullshit.
你他妈耍了我
It was a fucking play.
你从背后捅了我一刀
It was a play, it was a fucking move.
别在这娘们儿兮兮的
So, don't act like a cunt to me
老子才不吃你那一套
because it won't fucking wash!
好的 再见
Okay, bye.
他... 说了什么
What...what...what did he say?
有任何具体的法律或人身威胁吗
Any actual legal or, or physical threats?
算了 我没必要知道
You know what? Don't need that in my head.
就把那些内容写在邮件里 再发给你自己 以防后患
Just put it in an e-mail and send it to yourself, in case it comes up.
好了 各就各位
Okay. Action stations.
我给过他机会了 格丽
I gave him a chance. Gerri.
所有人 都过来
Everyone, let's go.
好的
Okay. Great.
我建议我给司法部打电话
So, I suggest I call DOJ
让他们知道
and just right away let them know
我们在得知这些指控后有多么震惊
how horrified we were to learn of these, um, allegations
所以打算成立一个特别委员会
and that we intend to form a special committee
还可以告诉他们我们考虑雇佣哪些白鞋律所[精英律所]...
and we can tell them which white shoe law firms...
我有想法 那就是我们正在考虑彻底调查
I have ideas, we are considering to thoroughly investigate
并迅速报告调查的结果
and promptly report back their findings.
这样 我们真的要合作吗
Right. But do we cooperate?
和政府吗 当然 我觉得必须合作
With the government? Yeah, I think we have to cooperate.
我们已经面临了重压...
I mean, we were under pressure already...
如果不合作呢
Unless we don't?
行是行 但这是现实世界
Yeah, but real world?
我们是家上市公司
I mean, this is a public company.
谁知道他们手里有什么 甚至能查到什么
We don't know what they have or what they might get.
我们只有一招可出
There's only one real play here.
要是我还不想这么快就亮底牌呢
And what if I don't want to pull down my panties down so fast?
那你就把吊桥拉起来
Then you pull up the draw-bridge.
这是有政治动机的 "来抓我们吧 狗日的"
It's politically motivated. "Come get us, motherfuckers."
我们怎么解释呢
What's our story?
就说... 他在利用那些可怜的女人
The story is... is that he's exploiting these poor women.
非常让人失望
And that's very sad.
你本来要栽培他当接班人
You were grooming him for the top.
但是呢 他是个瘾君子 他辜负了你
But you know? He's a junkie and he blew it.
他就是个可悲的混球 需要接受心理治疗
He's a bitter fuck up that needs psychiatric help.
当然 你是那个大反派
And of course you're the big baddie,
所以大家都会附和你
so everybody jumped on board.
那些文件怎么办
And what about these papers?
是假的 或者 被偷走了
Uh, they're fake. Or stolen,
要是真有的话 你还在担心那些文件吗
if they even exist. Are you worried about the papers?
怎么样 我们以公司盗窃罪追究他的责任
Hmm? We'll go after him for corporate theft.
虽然这么说你儿子不太合适
This is, you know, not nice thing to say about your son
但是或许你该把他千刀万剐 丢到哈德森河里
but maybe you chop him into a million pieces and toss him in the Hudson?
毁掉肯德尔 他的计划就四分五裂了
You destroy Kendall, it falls apart.
大家怎么看
What do we think?
股价如何
How's the price?
净值很稳定
Well, uh, net-net, it's steady.
但是机构正在抛售 以防我们因此倒闭
But institutions are dumping in case this kills us
阿拉伯人正在买进 确保桑迪和斯图尔特赢
and arbs are buying in case Sandy and Stewy win.
肯德尔改变了游戏规则
Yeah, Kendall has changed the game.
现在不合作有点... 太...
Noncooperation now, it's not... it's too...
外面情况太复杂了 我觉得风险很高
It's too hot out there. I think it's very high risk.
你要是怂 什么事情风险都大
Yeah, well, everything's high risk if you're a pussy.
-我不是吃素的 好吗  -这...
- Hey, I eat red meat. Okay? - Well...
我只是... 想想后果吧
I'm just...the repercussions.
但我觉得你眼光太狭隘了
Yeah, but I think you're looking too small.
我们迂回一下
We do a dance,
我们静候时机 直到换届那天
and we bide our time 'til the election.
泛美给老家伙的宣传再续一个任期
ATN anointy-nointy the Raisin for a second term?
新司法部长 到了那时
New Attorney General. And by then,
这事的热度就没那么大了
this has gotten a little stale,
肯德尔会自暴自弃 因为他最爱干这种事
Kendall will self-destruct because it's his favorite.
然后一切就他妈一笔勾销了
And this all fades the fuck away.
要是我不去揭结痂
If I stop picking at scabs,
也就是道歉 谁知道我们会走到哪一步才算完
saying, "Sorry," Who knows where we'll end up.
投机者和机会主义者的集体诉讼
Class actions from the chancers and opportunists.
只要承认了不法行为...
Admissions of wrongdoing...
-上亿的资金就流失了  -操
- Billions out of the door. - Fuck!
如果你现在给司法部长打电话 吼他一顿
If you were to call the AG right now and shout at him,
-我们可以看看能不能这样做吗  -雨果 你能不能看看
- could we find out if that'd be okay? - Hugo, can you find out
要是洛根给司法部长打电话会怎么样
what would happen if Logan called the AG?
拿下老家伙 直接从最高层入手
Get the Raisin. Let's go to the top.
去搞定总统吧
Let's get the President.
礼貌点 好吗
But gentle. Okay?
还有吗
Anything else?
我们要点吃的吗
Do we want to order some food?
吃的 吞口水就够了
Food? Swallow. We're on saliva
再靠靠肾上腺素 上了飞机再说 行吗
and adrenaline here, until we get on a plane. All right?
不要当地的食物
No local foods.
我出了问题 我们就完了
I get the shits, we're fucked.
-雨果 走了  -好
- Hugo! Let's go. - Okay.
我们已经在这逗留太他妈久了
We've lingered long e-fucking-nough!
好的 各位 往这走 飞机已经在停机坪上了
Okay, guys, uh, this way please. The plane's on the tarmac.
开始行动吧 我会再给你打回来
Let's get going. I will definitely call you back.
好的
Okay.
你上了热搜榜一
Uh, you're the number one trending topic,
在炸薯球前面
ahead of Tater Tots.
教皇关注了你
And the Pope followed you.
好的
Okay.
不对 这个... 是真的吗
Okay, no, this is not the... is this the real?
-不 好像不是真教皇  -好了 谢谢你 格雷格
- No, I don't think this is the Pope. - Right, great. Thanks Greg.
不 这是个教皇 不是那个教皇
No, it's, it's a pope. It's not the Pope.
弗兰克 听着 你不需要说话
Frank? Hey. Listen, you don't need to speak.
我只想说
I just want to say,
抱歉之前没跟你说 我就是想让你知道
sorry I didn't talk to you before, but I just want to let you know
我准备经营的公司里会有你的位置
there's a place for you in the company I'm gonna run.
你只用告诉他时间到了 好吗
You just need to tell him time's up, okay?
他退一步 我们就冷静下来
He steps back and we can cool this down.
像你这样的人出面 德高望重
Someone like you steps in, a lot of respect.
很多人都买你的账
You know, a lot of folks would put in a shift for you.
我们一起稳住大局
We steady the ship together.
好吗 我这么做都是为了你 朋友
Okay? I did this for you, man.
为了我们 为了这个公司的灵魂
Did this for us. For the soul of the company.
非常让人激动 弗兰克 好的
This is exciting, Frank. Okay.
-格丽 打给格丽  -好
- Uh, Gerri. Get me Gerri. - Okay.
直接转到语音信箱了
Oh, straight to voicemail.
通用航空
车到了
The vans are here.
通用航空
总统基本上是支持我们的
So, the President is basically supportive,
但是他们觉得今天最好还是
but they think it might be best for there
不要在白宫的日志里留下你们电话联系的记录
not to be a call with you on the White House log today.
妈的他不能打个私人电话吗
Like he can't make a fucking private call?
可以打给 米歇尔·安
We got offered Michelle-Anne.
那个难缠的女人吗
Oh, the pantsuit barnacle?
你想的话我可以打给她
I got her if you wanna.
不想 去他的 我不跟保姆说话
No. Fuck it. No. I don't talk to the babysitter.
你去试探她的口风
You fuckin' sound her out.
那就太好了 对 我等着
That'd be great. Yeah, Yeah I'll hold.
-卡尔呢  -他太想吃个三明治了
- Where's Karl? - Yeah. He really feels he needs a sandwich.
-三明治  -对 我本想说服他的 但是...
- A sandwich? - Yeah. I tried to tell him. But...
各位 这边还有一辆车
Guys, we have another van for you over here.
好吗 就在这边
Okay? Right this way.
米歇尔吗 我是格丽·吉尔曼 近来如何
Michelle? Gerri Kellman. How you doing?
请听我说 这就是胡说八道
Listen, I just wanted to say it was all nonsense
我们知道总统会支持我们
and we know the President will be supportive,
但我们还是想回答...
but we just wanted to answer...
愿意回答他的任何疑问
to, to offer to answer any questions he may have.
你好 好的
Hi, yeah,
格丽 我想他对洛根的困境十分同情
Gerri, I think he just feels for Logan at this difficult time.
好 那就告诉他我们不是在寻求帮助
Great, well, just let him know that we are not asking for favors.
我知道了
We hear you.
我们只是不希望 就资源而言
We just wouldn't, simply in terms of resources,
让司法部跟着肯德尔一起 陷入怨恨的无底洞
want DOJ to follow Kendall off down this rabbit hole of bitterness.
好的
Okay.
你知道总统非常敬重洛根
Well, you know how much the President respects Logan.
知道吧
Okay?
好 所以私下问一句
Great. So, off the record, um...
司法部态度如何
what's the temperature at Main Justice?
会有风险吗 还是说南部管区要对我们下手
Any danger of them or Southern District going Batman on this?
司法部长很明智
Um, the Attorney General is very smart.
我们都喜欢巴威克
Oh, we all love Bhavick.
他能识破诡计的 对吧
He'll... he'll see through this, right?
只是司法部副部长
It's just, the DAG likes to think
她性情耿直
she's something of a straight-shooter.
玛丽莲很难搞
Marilyn's prickly.
所以玛丽莲是你们唯一的问题
So that's your only issue, Marilyn.
不如你们直接开除她吧
Well, maybe you should just fire her!
呵呵
Ha, ha, ha.
-司法部并非无所不能  -他们可以的...
- Justice can't do nothing. - Well, they could...
我们也无能为力
It's out of our hands.
强硬一点就可以实现
Not if you grab it.
但是听着 我们不想和他闹矛盾
Um, but look, we don't want to fall out with him.
当然 他是总统
Well no, he's the president.
当然 那需要安排两位老人家
No, sure, but, do we want to get the old guys
亲自通个电话吗
on the blower so they can just chat for five?
不会有什么问题的 格丽
This will all be great, Gerri.
有事随时联系我 好吧
Just find me whenever, on anything, okay?
好 谢谢你的信息 非常感谢
Great, well, I appreciate getting a read. Um, many thanks.
好了 还行吗
Yeah. Good?
干得不错 基本上持支持态度
Good work. Basically supportive.
干得不错 格丽
Good work, Gerri.
好了 我们万事俱备了
Okay, we're, uh, fueled and tooled.
准备好去纽约"狂欢"了吗
We all set for New York City and a fuck fest?
格丽 留下
Gerri, stay.
借过 抱歉
Excuse me. Sorry.
小西...
Oh, Shiv...
小西 小西 小西
Shivy, Shivy, Shivy.
你那边怎么样
How are you doing over there?
准备好过来了吗 我给你留了位置
You ready to come over? I got a spot for you.
喂 喂
Hello, hello?
好了 杰西 我们有哪些人
Okay, Jess, what do we got?
我们有独立董事
Um, we have independent directors.
-不错  -意见领袖 重量级的
- Boom. - Opinion shapers, A list.
还有尤恩 莱尔德
And then we've got Ewan, Laird.
-好  -你妈妈...
- Good. - Your mom...
格雷格的母亲 乔希·阿伦森和玛西娅
Greg's mom, Josh Arenson, and Marcia?
-很好  -格雷格 怎么说...
- Great. - Oh, Greg. How's, uh...
我是说...
I mean...
头条新闻是
Headline is,
网络浩瀚 显然...
the internet is big, uh, obviously...
我还没有... 还不能... 还没来得及看完全部
and I haven't...I can't... I...I couldn't read it all,
但我正在努力看 我猜...
but I'm working through, I guess...
是的 这就是媒体监控的整体情况
Yeah. That's the big picture over here at Media Monitoring.
-风向是正面的吗 格雷格  -非常正面
- Is it positive, Greg? - It's super positive.
-非常正面吗  -是的
- Super positive? - Yeah.
负面内容也会给人留下一点印象
The negative stuff does tend to stick in the mind a little
因为它写得真切
just 'cause it's quite, uh, visceral.
但总体来说情况良好
But yeah. Basically, very good.
可爱的表情包和梗图 还有... 诸如此类
Nice memes, good memeage, and... and, uh, so on.
-喂  -内 你好哇
- Hello?  - Nae? Hey.
我有无数个电话要接 但我还是想打给你
I got a million calls, but I wanted to say hi.
你看到了吗
You see it?
看来你是世界上最厉害的男人了
Yeah, seems like maybe you're the best man in the world?
是的 我谢谢您嘞
Yeah, fuck you.
但我是说 也许你真的是
Yeah, but I mean, maybe you are.
好吧 呵呵 当然
Okay, ha, ha, ha, sure.
-但如果我真的是呢  -可不是嘛
- But what if I am? - No, sure.
但是说真的 肯 就说几句
But, um, seriously, Ken, just for a second here.
-如果你真的是呢  -肯
- What if you really are? - Um, Ken?
-什么  -我们快到了 所以…
- Yeah? - We're almost there, so...
内 我到韦斯达了 你能来找我吗
Uh, Nae, hey, I'm arriving at Waystar. Can you come see me?
雷米说他们可能想取消你的进入权限
Oh, um, Remi's saying that maybe they're trying to cancel your access?
-回聊 内 我爱你  -好
- Later, Nae. Hey, I love you. - Yeah.
好吧 他们不能
Okay, well...well... well, they can't.
当然 但他们可能已经取消了
Sure, but, uh, they maybe did?
好吧 去他的 继续开车
All right. Fuck it, keep driving.
有媒体在我家对吧
There's press at my place, yeah?
是的 所以我们要去哪里
Uh, yes. So, where are we going?
上帝 这太疯狂了
Oh, God. This is crazy.
简直就是O·J·辛普森
This is like...this is like O.J.
我是说 如果O·J·辛普森没杀过人的话
I...I mean, except if O.J. Never killed anyone.
谁说我没杀过人
Who said I never killed anyone?
-那个被杀的角色是谁  -自由的果汁 宝贝
- What character is that? - Juice is loose, baby!
格丽 你没事吧
Uh, Gerri. Are you okay?
是的 没事 都好
Yeah, great. All good.
准备去和雨果谈谈
Just gonna go talk to Hugo.
因为现在 看起来
Because now, we're gonna go, it looks like
我们要先去萨拉热窝
in the first instance, to Sarajevo.
什么鬼 萨拉热窝
What the fuck. Sarajevo?
我想米歇尔·安妮把他吓坏了
I think Michelle-Anne freaked him out.
这是其他的地点选项
Other places to consider.
巴林 波斯尼亚 科威特 黎巴嫩 马尔代夫
Bahrain, Bosnia, Kuwait, Lebanon, Maldives,
摩洛哥 卡塔尔 沙特阿拉伯 梵蒂冈
Morocco, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, the Vatican?
好吧 操
Okay. Fuck.
这些国家有什么共同点
What do all these countries have in common?
它们都是虚构的 都是龙之国度
They're all made up? They're lands with dragons!
不 我猜它们都没有和美国签订引渡条约
No, I imagine that none of them have an extradition treaty with the U.S.
-好吧 操  -我觉得我们可以这样
- Okay. Fuck. - You know, what I thought we could do,
悄悄地用更具诱惑力的赞助合同
um, is discreetly dangle some juicy contributor contracts
收买一些更负责任的检察官
to the more responsible prosecutors?
我们要去萨拉热窝
We're going to Sarajevo.
什么 去萨拉热窝 再说一遍 搞什么...
What? To Sarajevo? Excuse me, the fuck...
没事的 闭嘴吧
It's fine. Shut up.
大家听好
Hey. Look.
我不确定我有多少把握
I'm not sure how much cover I've got.
我需要给自己找个律师
I need to talk to a lawyer on my position.
谁能打赢这场硬仗
Who's a tough bastard?
什么 像莱欧·厄普顿那种吊人吗
What? Like a kind of Layo Upton type motherfucker?
女性比较合适 像丽莎·亚瑟那种
A woman would be great. Like a Lisa Arthur?
她打赢过妓女官司对吧
She did the hookers, right?
她给被拐的性工作者做过辩护 是的
She repped the trafficked sex workers, yes.
她的信誉是个加分项
It'd be great to have her credibility.
是的 有三四个备选的优秀女律师
Yeah. There are three or four good women,
但丽莎最有头脑 她能胜诉
but Lisa has an excellent brain. She is a winner.
如果你请莱欧 大家会说
You go with Layo, people will be like,
"他采取了焦土政策 他还有胜算"
"Oh, he's going scorched earth. Maybe he can fight this."
如果请丽莎 大家会说
We get Lisa, people will be like,
"天 也许真是放狗屁呢"
"Gee, maybe this is bullshit."
我请得到她吗
Can I get her?
那个 小西...
Well, uh, Shiv...
-可以 我...  -对吧
- Uh, yeah! I... - Right?
我是说 我...
I mean, you know? I'm...
她... 她是个很... 她是我朋友
She's...Yeah, she's a pretty... She's a friend.
-你能帮我请到她吗  -我不知道
- Could you get her for me? - I don't know. I mean,
她好胜心切 追求名利 所以...
she fucking loves winning and she loves money. So, uh...
-听着 听着  -我不...确定
- Listen. Listen. - I don't... know.
无论合作与否
Cooperate or not,
为了稳定董事会
to keep the board sweet,
我有必要适当抽身了
I may need to step back a little.
好吧 那谁将会...
Okay. Oh, well then, who would...
我现在不想回去 可以吗
I don't want to go back right now. Does that play?
我是说 我只是希望你平安
Yeah, I mean, I just... I, I want you safe.
-这才是最重要的  -是的
- That's the most important thing. - Yeah.
好了 好了 好了
Okay. Okay, okay, uh,
小西 罗曼 格丽要回去管理纽约的事务
Shiv, Roman, Gerri are gonna go back to manage New York.
我没必要像个挨打的女孩
No need for me to go running back
一样跑回去 面子上挂不住
like a slapped girl, looks weak.
-好 再找一架飞机  -需要我去吗
- Great! Another plane. - Want me to go?
不 不 不 我不信任你
No, no, no. I don't trust you.
你跟我一起 卡尔可以监督董事会的联络
You're gonna stay with me. Karl can monitor board liaison.
汤姆留在这 处理泛美的事务
Tom here, across ATN.
我亲自去请律师
I'll make the call on the lawyer.
我喜欢莱欧 但是我要考虑一下
I like... I like Layo, but, uh, I need to think about it.
在飞机上开紧急会议
Council of war on the plane!
走吧 滚边去 没用的小崽子
Go on, fuck off back there, Tumbledown Dick.
洛根 这架飞机现在改航飞萨拉热窝了
Logan, uh, this plane has now been rerouted to Sarajevo.
已经就绪了 我再去找一架飞机
It's ready to go. And, uh, I will get another plane.
洛根 你需要...
Uh, Logan? Do you need...
-康  -这个家伙
- Oh, Con? - This guy? Yeah.
康 对 对 你很重要
Con, yes, yes, yes. Very important.
你可以在这留守吗 确保这里一切无恙
Can you hold the fort here? Can you keep this all secure?
你的意思是 就我们两个人来守住巴尔干半岛吗
You mean hold down the Balkans with just two divisions?
我可以试试
I can try.
再见 祝你们一路顺风
See you guys. Have a good trip.
谢谢
Thanks.
听着 我的人取得联系了 他们想知道
Oh, listen, my guy made contact and they wanna know
我们想不想给戏剧做推广营销
if we wanna do a marketing push with the play.
-然后呢  -你知道吗
- Okay. - You know?
从负面言论的角度
The whole hate watch angle,
选出最糟糕的评论
uh, you know, like, pick out all the worst reviews
比如 "买了票的话 自杀还不晚"
like, you know, "Kill yourself if you got a ticket,"
或是说是中了蛊
or the one about brain poison.
行了 我都知道 谢谢你 老康
Yeah, okay, I know all of them, Con. Thank you.
-真"贴心"  -对 利用自我讽刺
- That's so sweet. - Right. So, jump on the irono-cycle
制造一个热点
and, uh, make it into a thing
吸引潮人和混蛋
for the hipsters and the dipshits.
我们就能扳回一成
We could make a nice little return.
行吧 行 听起来很有趣
Sure. Yeah, I mean. Yeah. That sounds exciting.
对吧
Yeah?
我们回头再...
Hey, so, we'll talk about things...
-谈谈是吧  -对 对
- when we get back, right? - Oh, yeah, yeah.
-好的 行  -当然 可以的
- Yeah? Okay. Cool. - Of course. Yeah, okay. So, yeah.
因为我爱你
You know, 'cause I love you.
谢谢 谢谢你
Thanks. Thank you.
对了 别...
And, uh... Yeah, don't...
你会再见到他的
You'll see him again.
汤姆 我当然还会见到他啊
Well, yeah, obviously I'll see him again, Tom.
-你为什么要说这种话  -小西 我只是想安慰你
- Why would you say that?  - I'm being nice, Shiv.
如果你是在担心他回不来的话
If you're worried that he won't come home,
我觉得这不可能 所以...
I think that's unlikely. Okay, so...
这我知道
Well, I know that.
好 没事
Okay. Great. It's fine.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
对了 肯有打给你吗
Oh, did Ken call you?
肯 打给我吗 没有啊 绝对没有
Ken? Me? No. No, no, no.
没聊过 怎么了 他打给你了吗
Not to speak. No. Why, did he call you?
-没有  -没有
- No. - No.
没有 只是好奇
No. No, I was just wondering.
-好的 那照顾好他  -好的
- Okay. Well, look after him. -Okay.
-保持联系  -好的
- Keep in touch. - Okay.
这里是个安全的地方吧
So, just...This is a safe place to be, yeah.
直接放我进去就好
So just buzz me in.
别用我的推特账号发推
Don't tweet from RealKendallRoy.
-我没... 我没有用你的账号  -我说真的
- I'm not... I'm not tweeting from your account. - I'm serious.
我没有 我是用自己的账号
I'm not. I'm tweeting from my account.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
-在这等我一下  -好的
- Just chill here for a second. - Right.
你好 你好
Hello, hello!
-你没事吧 还好吗  -我很好
- Are you okay? How are you doing? - I'm good.
-你确定吗  -确定
- You're good? - Yeah. Yeah.
方便我把人带进来吗
Is it okay if I bring in the guys?
当然 他们被检查过了吗
Sure. Are they vetted?
-对 他们都很规矩 杰西  -对的
- Yeah. They're legit, right, Jess? - Yeah.
-所有阿联酋人都用这家保安公司  -都检查过了 我确定
- All the Emirati use the firm. - Yeah, vetted. Totally.
那可太好了
Oh, well, amazing.
介意我打几通电话吗
So, is this okay to, to do a few calls?
如果有别的选择 我也不会问你了
I wouldn't ask if I had options.
可以 可以
Yes, yes.
-谢谢你  -没事
- Thank you. - Of course.
-谢谢 拉瓦  -嗯
- Thanks, Rava. - Yeah.
-格雷格  -我来关门
- Hey, Greg. - I'll close it up.
好的
Yeah, good.
所以
So, hey.
-你真的做了  -我他妈的确实做了
- You really did it, huh? - I fucking did it.
对 邮件里也都在说
Yeah, well, it's been in the mail.
确实是
It has been in the mail.
你之前说过 不这么做
You know, like you always said, it was either this
还不如去阿索斯山当修道士
or, you know, go to Mount Athos and become a monk.
-对 阿索斯山有个修道院  -阿索斯山
- Oh, yeah. This monastery on Mount Athos. - Mount Athos.
那个选择可能更为合理
That, that, that could have been a more logical choice.
想不到吧
Surprise, surprise.
你来这是为了什么 一个...
You came here for what? A, uh...
-鼓励吗  -不 只是
- pat on the back? - No, just,
为了躲开媒体 他们把我家围个水泄不通
the press. They're, they're swarming mine.
我 我需要一个适合开会的藏身之处
And I, I need a hiding hole for meetings.
而且 我也真的想见到你和孩子们
Plus, I actually wanted to see you and the kids.
我 其实...
You know, I, kind of, like...
这其实是为了你们做的
It was kind of for you guys.
是吗...
Yeah, well...
我...
Hey, hey, I...
我没看发布会 但是...
I didn't see it but I've just...
工作时有人问起这事 但...
I've been up against it at work but...
-大家都说你做得不错  -好的
- people were saying you did great. - Oh. Yeah.
对 还行吧 随便吧
Yeah, it was... it was fine, whatever.
你应该会想看看
You might want to watch it.
-不 我会...  -你应该会想
- No, I... - You might want to.
我 我在联系丽莎·亚瑟
You know, I'm, I'm, I'm talking to Lisa Arthur.
不错 她很有名
Oh, great. Well, yeah, she's famous.
她是最厉害的 你觉得如何
She's the best. So, what you think?
我可以做到吗 我能赢吗
Can I do this? Can I win?
-肯 我不知道  -不 没事
- I don't know, Ken. - No. Right.
没事的
Right.
你感觉如何
How you feeling?
我很期待能多多观赏巴尔干半岛
I'm looking forward to seeing more of the Balkans.
这是最糟的情况了吗
Is this the worst?
之前有小报自杀事件
Well, there were the tabloid suicides.
当时我们差点因为阿根廷炸了
When we nearly went kablooey because of Argentina.
-我知道  -天安门和解事件
- I know. - The Tiananmen Accommodations?
莎丽·安走后的乌云危机[指当时罗根糟糕的状态]
The Black Cloud after Sally Ann?
-我记得  -我不知道
- I remember. - I don't know.
他总是能起死回生
He's the comeback kid.
不 我知道 我知道
No, I know, I know, I know.
但是 有参议院 联邦调查局
But, Senate, FBI.
美国证券交易委员会 集体诉讼
SEC, Class Actions.
再加上桑迪和斯图伊
Plus Sandy and Stewy?
这是个12英尺长的剧毒树蛙三明治套餐
I mean, this is a 12-foot sub of poisonous tree frogs.
这是混了31种窒息口味的芭斯罗缤冰淇淋
This is the full Baskin-Robbins 31 flavors of fucker right there.
先生们
Gentlemen?
不好意思 能回避下吗 谢谢
Excuse me, do you mind? Thank you.
好 我决定这么办事
So, this is where I'm landing.
韦斯达方面 找个三家顶级白鞋律所
For Waystar, three white shoe firms on retainers.
再和仅次于他们的五家事务所暗通款曲
Then the next best five, let's play footsie.
试着用利益冲突让他们和我们一伙
See if we can tie them up with conflicts.
你们两位 和参议院众议院的代表接洽
You two, touch base with Senate and House surrogates,
我台的正职评论员和朋友们
payroll commentators, and friends.
所有人都要请个律师
I want everyone lawyered up.
汤姆 我要过目泛美网络就此事播报的所有社论
Tom, me to see editorial on anything on this across ATN
还有国际频道和纸质媒体
and global cable and print outlets.
我们给其他公司施压 要点是
We pressure-point other operations, the line is,
"别相信敌方言论 纯粹不靠谱的混蛋
"Don't lean on this, it's as bendy as fuck.
今天放聪明点 明天就不会像个傻逼"
Play it smart today, you won't look a cunt tomorrow."
卡尔 我需要你在三十分钟内
Karl, I need to talk to the top 12 shareholders
联系前十二大的股东们
in the next 30 minutes.
尽快召开紧急董事会议
An emergency board meeting ASAP
一直给我开到下周 好吗
and they'll be rolling through 'til next week, okay?
雨果 我刚说的很明白了 你也在处理了吧
Hugo, I imagine most of that is obvious and in train, right?
一切都在掌控之中
Largely in hand. Largely in hand.
很好 那关于合作事宜...
Great. And in terms of cooperation...
开战了
It's war!
滚开
Fuck off!
这是战争 滚开
It's war. Fuck off.
-行吗  -行
- Good? - Good.
-是的  -不过
- Yeah. - But
给他们来这招
we throw them this.
我会退下执行总裁的位子
I'll step back as CEO.
-什么...  -你确定吗
- Wha... - You sure?
当然 在公司运营方面
Well, obviously, on operational matters
我将不会正式参与
I will expect to have, um, informal input.
所以 我退位时 暂时地
So, as I step back, uh, temporarily,
我们要选谁当执行总裁
who do we like as CEO?
我他妈不在乎
I don't give a fuck.
不过是个名号
Its name plates.
来啊 一吐为快
Come on. Brain dump.
说话啊 百花齐放
Speak. Let a hundred flowers bloom!
不会记仇的
No come-backs.
我必须得说 我还不错吧
Well, I have to say, uh, I look good.
什么 怎么了 为什么不 我不错啊
What? What? Why not? I like me.
真是我们要找的"新鲜面孔"
Just the fresh face we're looking for.
弗兰克 去你的
Oh, fuck off, Frank.
卡尔 如果你的手是干净的
Karl, if your hands are clean
只是因为你光顾的妓院会帮你美甲
it's only because your whorehouse also does manicures.
我想你是要从孩子们中挑选 或是格丽
I mean, I imagine you're looking at a kid. Or Gerri?
但如果你想 找个短期的人选...
But if you want...if you want someone short term...
-弗兰克  -了解公司的一切 我...
- Frank? - who knows the place inside out, I...
你当不了的
You're not trusted.
-你就是一坨烂泥  -好吧 我明白了 行
- You're mashed potatoes. - Okay. I get it. Yep.
我当然希望我的孩子接任
Now, I'd like a kid, obviously.
所以 小西还是罗曼
So, Shiv or Roman.
我们倾向于女性 那就小西或者格丽
But we'd love a woman. So, Shiv or Gerri.
我又想要个有经验的 所以 罗曼...
But I'd like experience. So, Roman...
还是格丽
or Gerri.
我得去趟洗手间
Just gonna run to the bathroom.
选女人... 不错
A woman is... a woman is good.
-喂  -听我说 他们正在隔壁
- Hello? - Hey, listen. They're playing
和上帝对赌呢
fucking dice with God next door, okay?
他现在就在挑选新的执行总裁
He is picking a new CEO in real time.
等会 我去看一下
Okay. Let me just check that.
稍等一下
One second.
-什么 临时代理吗  -对 没错
- What? Interim? - Sure, sure.
但你也懂的 谁知道这事要闹多久
But you know, who knows how long it will last?
德国大众弄了差不多有五年吧
VW took like, 5 years, right?
-沃尔玛用了十年  -现在口风如何
- Wal-Mart took a decade. - And what's the temperature?
没有 还在自由讨论
It's, you know, it's free form.
大家在"百花齐放"
"Let a hundred flowers bloom."
好的 知道了
Yeah, right! Sure!
那 你想当吗
So listen, do you want it?
我 什么
Me? What?
不 你疯了吧 小西 我不认为...
No. You crazy, Shiv? I don't think that's even...
经历过听证会和邮轮风波 我不觉得...
I don't think with the hearings and cruises...
我不觉得 不行... 我不行 我干不了
I don't think it's...I don't, I don't...I think, no, I mean.
-不  -你是想推我一把
- No. - So, you're okay to push me?
废话 我正是要确定这一点
Well, sure. That's what I wanted to know.
因为他说他会奋战到底
Because he's gonna fight, he says.
你准备好成为他的代表了吗
You wanna be the face of that?
我是觉得 这事也没有十全十美的解决办法吧
Yeah, I mean, you can get too fucking clever with this
你说呢
can't you?
你在里面没事吧 朋友 找不到静脉注射吗
Have a problem in there, buddy? Can't find a vein?
等会儿 傻逼 说话注意点
Hold on. Watch it, fuckhead!
我得挂了 如果有机会 你想上任吗
Okay, I gotta go. But, if it's going, you want it?
我可不想像郝薇香小姐那样 满脑子谋略大志
I don't wanna be buried like Miss Haversham with a fucking bonnet
[英国作家查尔斯·狄更斯"远大前程"中的人物]
却他妈被生活埋没 所以当然 我想当
full of clever stratagems. So, yeah! Yes. Yes, I want it.
你赶紧回去奋力争取 宝贝 快点
You get in there and you hustle, baby. Hustle!
好
Okay.
-电话挺有意思啊  -什么
- Interesting call? - What?
没有 只是… 扯犊子
No. Just...just bullshit.
扯犊子 那也太无趣了吧
Just bullshit? That's boring.
我讨厌无趣的事 你呢
I hate boring shit, don't you?
-什么  -就是 无聊的电话
- What? - Just, you know, boring phone calls
扯些有的没的 太无聊了吧 小西
about bullshit. It's just so boring, right, Shiv?
真的很无聊吗
It's boring?
因为格丽刚从弗兰克那得到消息
Because Gerri just heard from Frank
显然爸正在挑选新的执行总裁呢
and Dad is apparently live picking the new CEO.
知道了
Okay.
"知道了" 汤姆刚才没和你说吗
"Oh, okay." So, Tom didn't just mention that to you?
既然你都提到了 或许他也跟我说了
Yeah, now that you mention it, he, maybe he did.
是啊 或许吧 你他妈的
Yeah, okay, maybe. Fuck you. Fuck you.
弗兰克为什么打电话给你 你又为什么要告诉他
So, how come Frank called you and how come you told him?
我只是心直口快罢了 小西
I'm just a very straightforward person, Shiv.
是吗 那你听到了什么消息
Yeah? So, what'd you hear?
我听说提到了好多人的名字
Well, I heard there's a number of names in contention.
真不错 不打算玩点更有意思的吗
All right! Care to make it interesting
来赌一把怎么样
Throw a little money on the table?
我觉得已经够有意思了
Well, I'm already pretty fucking interested.
所以 我还是算了
So, I think I'm good.
当然 全部注销...
Yeah, a full tally would be...
那就太好了 谢谢 我可以等
would be great, thank you. Yep. I can hold.
你好
Hi
想转告你一声 我帮他进行媒体监控
Kinda just wanna let you know, I was doing his media monitoring
一段时间了 但我猜
for a while, but I guess
后面你会接管吧
you'll be taking that over?
没错 后面我们来
Yeah, that would be us.
好的 我记下了很多推文
Yeah, I wrote down a lot of tweets,
一些感觉相对重要的相关推文 以便...
like relevant tweets that felt kind of important so I could...
-交给你们会有用吗 还是...  -我们能找到
- Is that useful to pass on? Or... - We can find them.
-都在推特上对吗  -对
- They're on Twitter? - Yeah.
全都... 都在推特上
They are all on... They're all on Twitter.
-没错  -还是谢谢你
- Yeah. - But thank you.
客气 随时听候差遣
No worries. Here to help.
我在这里待命
I'm on hold over here.
帮我妈注销信用卡
Cancelling my mom's credit card.
不错
Okay. Nice.
是的 但 事实上这样有点蠢
Yeah, no. It's pretty stupid actually.
我爷爷断绝了给她的资金支持
My grandpa cut her off.
说来话长 我给她了一张金卡
Long story. I guaranteed her gold card
因为我觉得这才是 一个孝顺的儿子
just 'cause I thought that'd be, like, a good son thing to do?
她看完新闻发布会后 她就有点
And then just she saw the press conference, and she's kind of like,
认为肯会把整个公司搞垮
under the impression that Ken's taking the company down.
所以她恐慌性抢购纽崔布里特榨汁机
And so she's over here panic buying NutriBullets
以及克鲁格金币 就是某种货币
and buying a lot of Krugerrands. Like a very particular currency.
她甚至都没喝过果昔...
And she never even drinks the smoothies...
这就像...
So, it's like...
大名鼎鼎的贝里·施耐德驾到
Berry fucking Schneider in the house!
非常欢迎 最近怎么样
Thanks for coming. How you doing?
-还好 很高兴见面  -是吧
- Great. Good to see you. - Yeah?
来 进来坐 进来坐
Come on in. Come on in. Let's sit, let's sit.
-感谢邀请我们  -我是肯德尔
- Thanks for having us. - Hey, I'm Kendall.
我是康福莉
Comfry.
-他在骚扰你吗  -没有 他挺好的
- Is he harassing you? - No, he's fine.
格雷格 在这待着
Greg, stay here.
欢迎来到我前妻的客厅 坐吧 坐吧
Welcome to my ex-wife's living room. Sit, sit.
我们就开门见山了 有些工作是为了钱
Can we just say right off, some jobs are money jobs
有些工作是心之所向
some are heart jobs.
我们非常愿意和您合作 我们很喜欢您的叙述
We would love to work with you. We love the narrative arc.
我们欣赏您的各方各面
We love everything you did.
我也非常希望能和你们合作
And I would love to work with you,
容我问一句 我知道你们是业内最好的
but, if it's cool, and I know you guys are the best
但我能先听听你们的提案吗
but is it okay if this is still a pitch?
-那当然  -非常好
- Of course! - Great.
-我们有很多想法  -请说
- So, we have a lot of thoughts. - Yeah.
包括传媒策划和定位规划
Communication planning and positioning thoughts.
还有我们怎么利用
How we can leverage our relationships
-和主流媒体各大作家之间的关系  -嗯 对
- with significant writers at major outlets. - Yes. Yes.
准备放大一些引人注目非主流媒体的作用
Prepare to prime and amplify some impressive secondaries.
很好 非常好 我能说几句吗
Great, great. So, shall, shall I talk, or will you?
我们当然想听听您的意见
Well, we want to hear your thoughts of course,
但您要先听完我们的五个要点吗
but you wanna start off just hearing our five points?
当然 当然 请继续
Sure. Sure, you go.
-那好 所以…  -我觉得标题应该是
- Okay. So... - But I think the headline needs to be
"什么风云突变 我们即将改变文化气候"
"Fuck the weather, we're changing the cultural climate."
-但你继续吧  -好 我想说的是...
- But you go. - Okay, I mean...
正文就写 我与纽约时报商讨接受特约采访
For context, I, I, I'm talking to the Times about an op-ed.
起草另一份企业宣言
Draft an alternative corporate manifesto.
然后放一个TED的快问快答 诸如此类
Drop a rapid reaction TEDx. Shit like that.
这个想法非常不错
Well, that's great.
非常俗气 但是
It's cheesy as fuck but, you know,
我想要展现出顺理成章的思想体系
I need people to see this was part of a coherent philosophy,
不只是胖揍了那老头一拳
not just punching an old guy in the fucking nose?
-对吧  -没错 没错 我们想法一致 所以...
- Yeah? - Right. Right. That's in line with our thoughts. So...
我只是要说 依我的愚见
Well, I just, I may as well say, on a dumb level,
我希望我的推特能畅所欲言
I'd like my Twitter to be off the hook.
表现出非常真诚恳切
This could all get super earnest,
我打算找一些"马男波杰克"这类的人
so I was thinking of hitting up some BoJack guys.
言辞较为尖刻讥讽的年轻人...
You know? Some, some, some of the Lampoon kids...
把对面碾在脚下 让我的话成为
to just smash that shit, make my feed a little powder keg
人人都想追看的重磅炸弹
people need to check-in with?
用酷推文来表达立场吗
Like cool tweets that position you?
没错 那就是...
Yeah, that would be the...
老掉牙的说法 "酷推文"
straight-leg chino way of putting it. "Cool tweets."
-去你的  -去你的
- Fuck you! - Fuck you!
开个玩笑 我知道你们是最棒的
No, it's...I'm kidding. I know you guys are the best.
好的 抱歉 我非常希望和你们合作
Okay, sorry. I want to work with you
但是... 你们愿意和我共事吗
if you can... if you can work with me?
当然
Sure.
我们认为您会胜出 我们就喜欢赢家
Well, we think you're going to win this and we like winners!
完美
Hell yeah.
克莱奥酒店
-你好  -你好 韦斯达·罗伊科
- Hello. - Hi, Waystar Royco?
-格丽没有被牵扯吧 对吗  -某种程度上
- Gerri is clean, right? - Well, I mean. Up to a point
她和邮轮八竿子打不着 那时候...
She was nowhere near cruises was she, when... you know?
她当时在英国处理监管的破事
She was in the UK on all that regulatory shit,
就出事那段时间
I think, during the time in question.
不得不说 我觉得格丽不错
I have to say, I like Gerri.
你觉得格丽不错
You like Gerri?
是的
I do.
这是以退为进吗 孩子
Are you playing the reverse banjo, son?
准备抹黑她吗
Trying to black spot her?
不 不 当然没有
Nope. No. I do.
她非常沉着冷静 我觉得罗曼也不错
She's very stolid. And I like Roman.
你觉得罗曼也不错
You like Roman?
-那你自己呢 汤姆  -我吗 别逗了
- What about yourself, Tom? - Who, me? What?
对啊 你也算家里人
You know. You're kind of family.
算是新鲜血液
Kind of new blood.
太客气了 但是... 我不知道
Well, that's very kind. But I don't...no. I don't...
我来这个家的时间还很短 所以...
I think it's a little rich for my blood just yet. So...
-小西怎么样  -小西很棒
- What about Shiv? - Well, Shiv's great.
我喜欢小西 但她经验不足 至于罗曼 他很棒 但是...
I like Shiv. But no experience. And Roman, great, but...
-你觉得罗曼还没准备好吗  -你觉得呢
- You don't think Roman is ready? - Do you?
有人准备好了吗
Well, is anybody ready?
-难道我准备好了吗  -所以...
- Was I ready? - So...
他也没有整天"啥啥啥"...
When he's not all fucking "Meh, meh, meh"...
而且我还会在幕后指示 对吧
Plus, I'll be pulling the strings. Right?
-我喜欢罗曼  -我喜欢罗曼
- I like Roman. - I like Roman.
我当然喜欢罗曼
Of course I like Roman.
你当然支持 他会在上任的第一天就把你开了
Sure you do! He'll fucking fire you on day one!
罗慕路斯
Oh, Romulus.
爸 我能跟你谈谈吗
Hey, Dad. Can I just speak to you for a moment?
当然
Sure.
你在考虑的事情已经传出来了
Well, um, it's already getting out what you're thinking about
我只是想往这事情里
so, um, I just wanted to throw a couple of things
加点码
in the old, uh, lobster pot.
我觉得应该选我
I think it should be me.
-你说  -该轮到我了
- Okay. - It's my time.
我想要这个位置 我也能做到 所以...
I can do it, I want it, and I think I can do it. So...
-但是 抱歉 你说什么  -好的...
- But, I... Sorry, what? - Okay...
不 你接着说吧
No, no. You go.
好的
Yeah, okay.
我觉得你应该选我
I think it should be me.
但是...
But...
如果你觉得我还没准备好...
If you don't think I'm ready, okay, which...
我也能理解
I would understand.
但... 不是说我同意这个观点 但是...
But...and I'm not saying that I agree with that, but, you know...
也许在你的羽翼下成长几年...
maybe a couple of years under the wing of an older, uh... hen,
你就能看到我脱胎换骨
could, you know, see me crack out of the old egg.
而且我得说
And, um, I gotta, I gotta say,
我知道你一直很疼小西
I know that you've been sweet on Shiv,
身为哥哥 我也很爱她
and I love her, like a brother.
但是 我觉得现在还不是时候
But, um, I just don't think that it's time, you know?
抛开所有恩怨不说
And all bitterness aside,
我在想是不是该轮到格丽了
I do wonder if maybe it isn't Gerri time.
我在想 不如让铁石心肠的格丽试试
So I would think just, you know, let the stone-cold bitch do it.
她很强硬 是名女性
She's tough, she's got the good chromosomes.
无论如何 如果不是小罗时代 那么...
For whatever reason, it ain't Romey time, then...
也许是狐朋狗友时代
maybe it's crony time.
希望我没有越界
I hope I haven't, um, I don't know, overstepped here.
没有 谢谢你 儿子
Nope. Thank you, son.
好的 我很想要这个位置 但我也理解
Okay, well, um, I'd love it, but, you know, I understand.
但我真的很想要 好吗
But I do want it. Okay?
但是 不会怀恨在心 所以...
But, you know? No hard feelings, so...
不管怎么说 我只是...
Yeah, no, anyway, I'm just...
爱你 爸爸
So, uh, uh yeah, love you, Dad.
再见
Bye.
罗曼出局了
Roman's out.
他出局了 好吗
He's out. Okay?
爸
谁的电话 你爸爸吗
Who is it? Is it him?
好的 当然
Yeah, yeah, of course.
爸 谢谢你 当然 我可以胜任
Thanks, Dad. Yeah. Sure, I can do that.
完全没问题
I can do it.
什么 你可以做什么
What? You can do what?
我靠 你说吧
Oh, fuck. Fuck, go on.
-他希望我把丽莎请来  -你也太贱了
- He wants me to go get Lisa. - You're a fucking bitch.
他还让我告诉你在机场旁边等他
He told me to tell you to wait airport adjacent though,
他可能需要人搞定投资者
he might need someone on investors.
你可能得飞到波士顿见阿伦森
You might need to fly to Boston to meet Arenson.
或者劫持一架飞机 带他去古巴
Or, you know, hijack a plane and fly him to Cuba.
他没提到执行总裁的事吗
And he didn't say anything about CEO?
不好意思 他说了 是我
Oh, yeah. No, sorry, he did. It's me.
你骗到我了
You got me.
小西 你真的骗到我了
Oh, you really fooled me, Shiv.
太滑稽了
Hilarious.
我们已经看过了 所以现在怎么解决
We've gone over that, so now, what's the solution?
好的 什么时候
Okay. Well, when is that happening?
-马上  -好的
- Eminently. - Okay, good.
你们能先出去一下吗
Can I have the room, please?
-你好  -小西 你好
- Hey. - Hey, Shiv.
丽莎 最近怎么样
Lisa! How are you?
-挺好的  -看看你
- Good. - God, look at you!
-好久不见了 这个地方...  -快坐
- It's been so long. This place... - Sit, sit.
太棒了
Wow, it's amazing.
谢谢你
Thank you.
所以 我就直说了
So, So listen. I'm just gonna jump right in
我也不想为难我的朋友
because I don't want this to be difficult with a friend.
希望我没有浪费你的时间 因为...
Um, and I hope I've not wasted your time because...
没关系 我已经收到你的消息了
Yeah, no, the message came through.
-你不能代理我爸爸  -对
- You can't act for my dad. - Right.
我认为不合适 所以...
I don't think I fit, so...
好的
Yeah.
既然话都挑明了 我想和你聊聊
So, cards on the table, I wanted to
关于别的事情
talk to you about something else.
好的
Oh. Okay.
我...
I'm, uh...
我在考虑我自己的处境
Yeah, I'm thinking about my own position here.
说实话 我希望得到朋友的帮助
And to be honest, I could do with a friend.
一个谨言慎行且受过法律专业训练的朋友
A discreet friend with legal training.
一位参谋
You know, a consigliere.
一个聪明睿智的
A smart, savvy woman, who can help me navigate
可以帮助我找到定位的女性
the position I find myself in.
好的 谢谢夸奖
Right, that's kind.
但我一般不会出任这种角色
But that's not the kind of role I normally take on.
我知道 但是
I know, I know, but,
小丽 说实话 我别无选择了
honestly, Lis, I got nowhere to fucking turn here.
你知道我老公参与了这场恶战
You know my husband is a player in this.
某个世界里 我将出任执行总裁
And, in one world, there's, I'm in a position to come out here as CEO.
或者我可能需要离开公司来保护我的名声
Or I might have to leave the firm to protect my reputation.
我不知道我爸做了什么 也不知道我哥做了什么
You know, I don't know what my dad did, and I don't know what my brother did
我不知道这公司做了什么
and I don't know what the firm did.
丽莎 我真是他妈的一团糟
I'm in a fucking fuck pie here, Lisa.
我能收拾好这个局面吗 我不清楚
Can I clean it up? I don't know.
我不知道 我确实有个计划...
I don't know. I have a plan...
但我很容易被这两个男人搞垮
but I could easily get crushed between these two fucking men,
我需要找到出路 而且我需要和一个
and I need to game things out, and I need to do that
能给我法律 文化 政治 社会方面建议的人
with someone who can give me a read legally and culturally
一起做这件事
and politically and socially, and,
很复杂 我信任你 而且...
you know, it's a lot. And I trust you and...
好的 小西 别说了
Okay, look. Okay, look. stop. Stop, Shiv.
我不能给你提供法律建议
I can't give you legal advice
你也不该向我透露机密信息
and you should not give me any confidential information.
-好吗  -好的
- Okay? - Okay.
靠
Uh, fuck.
抱歉 是我...
I'm sorry. Is that...Does...
是我想的那样吗
Does that mean what I think it means?
-我们说完了吗  -说完了 你知道吗
- Are we done? - Yeah, you know what?
我想说...
I would, I would just say...
宝贝 好好把握住方向
careful who you hitch your wagon to, honey,
很多人都会阴沟里翻船
'cause a lot of wagons are going in the ditch.
好的 谢谢你 "宝贝"
Right. Thanks, "Honey."
你真的考虑和那个惺惺作态的傻逼合作吗
You know, you'd actually consider working with that
小丽 他根本就不真诚
disingenuous little fuck doll? He's not on the level, Lis.
小西 我不能帮你
Shiv, I am unavailable to help you.
如果情况有变 我会告诉你的
If for some reason that changes, I'll let you know.
-好吗  -好的
- Okay? - Okay.
谢谢你 好姐妹
Well, thanks, pal.
-有什么感觉吗  -关于什么
- Any vibes? - On what?
"关于什么" 关于整个
"On what?" On the whole,
"我爸是不是要去坐牢"的情况
"Is my dad going to jail?" Situation,
谁爬上了奥林匹斯山成为了新宙斯
who's climbing Mount Olympus to be the new Dr. Zeus.
看看我们在这 等待
Look at us here. Waiting.
真是... 好热
So fucking... hot.
如果是你 你够清白吗
If it's you, you think you're clean?
当然 这儿有张床
Yeah, obviously. There's a bed through here
如果你想要可以来一发
if you wanna give it a go.
邮轮女孩们被一波波地送到西边时
The pipeline was still sending cruise girls out west
你还在洛杉矶 对吗
when you were in L.A. Though, right?
那时... 差不多结束了
Yeah, that was... mostly over.
弗兰克认为推诿不知情就行
There's deniability, Frank thinks.
我们实际上基本啥都不知道
We essentially didn't even actually know.
那都是... 小伙计们和莫里斯做的
That's all on the... the little guys and Mo.
那加速推进卫星发射呢
What about the satellite launch, accelerating it?
我可能床技不太好 但我会好好地干你
I'd lay you badly, but I'd lay you gladly.
罗曼 我提醒你一下 目前就我看来
Can I remind you, Roman, that so far as I am concerned
我和你之间没有发生过什么
nothing has ever happened between us
只是纯粹工作往来
other than of a professional nature.
你一定很好奇吧
Gotta be curious though, right?
全盛时期的年轻斗士
Young fighter in his prime.
技术生涩 但是很饥渴
Technically raw, but, you know, hungry.
我算是个成功人士 罗曼
I am quite a successful person, Roman,
而我通过躲避麻烦来保持成功
and I remain so by avoiding mess.
我们被困在这个房间里
Well, we're stuck in this room for...
天知道会困多久 而且...
I don't even know how long. And...
没人会知道
no one would know.
喂 洛根 好的
Hey, Logan. Okay.
很好
Great.
好的 那... 好吧
Okay, uh, well... Okay. Well...
好的 好的
Yes, yes.
当然 我会转告他 我会跟他说的
Sure, I'll let him know. I'll tell him.
谢谢
Thank you.
-怎么说  -是我
- So? - It's me.
-你在开玩笑吧  -是我
- Are you kidding? - It's me.
-你在开玩笑吗  -我没在开玩笑
- Are you kidding? - I'm not kidding.
-真的是你  -是我 小西没请到丽莎
- It's actually you? - It's me. Shiv blew it with Lisa.
好吧
Okay.
我的天呐 所以是怎样 你现在是我老板了吗
Shit a pony. So, what, you're like the boss of me now?
这个嘛...
Well...
恭喜你 格丽 这...
Congratulations, Gerri. That's, uh...
这太棒了 恭喜
Yeah, that's great. Congratulations.
小婊贝
You fucking bitch.
这基本上只是个行政岗位 所以...
It's just an administrative position, largely, so...
你知道吗 我或许还 助了你一臂之力
You know, I might have swung this for you, you know that?
-那么... 谢谢  -真的
- Well, thank you. - Yeah.
小西知道吗
Does Shiv know?
我能告诉她吗 我...我觉得我该告诉她
Can I tell her? I...I think I should tell her.
她最好是从我这里听到消息
I think it'd be nicer coming from me.
-喂  -喂
- Yeah? - Hey, yeah.
我们没请到丽莎吗 我猜你是不是搞砸了
So, we lost Lisa? I guess you fucked it?
你朋友不喜欢你吗
Your friend doesn't like you?
还有格丽拿到了那份工作 他想让我转告你
Oh, also Gerri got the job. He wanted me to tell you.
但我要给你唱首歌 是这么唱的...
But I got a song for you. It goes...
♪ 你朋友不喜欢你 呜呜 呜呜 ♪
♪ Your friend doesn't like you Boo-hoo, boo-hoo ♪
♪ 爸爸也想炒了你 哦吼 哦... ♪
♪ And Dad wants to fire you woo-hoo, woo... ♪
♪ 然后你把电话挂了 ♪
♪ And you hung up! ♪
管他呢  我改主意了
You know what? Change of plan.
-嗨 拉瓦 你在吗  -在
- Hey, Rav? Rav? - Yeah.
-还有些人要来  -好的
- Hey, I got more folks incoming. - Yeah.
还有就是...
And, and also just, um...
提前知会一声 内奥米·皮尔斯上来没事吧
as an FYI, is it cool if Naomi Pierce comes up?
-当然 她是...那个皮尔斯  -她是...
- Sure, is she the Pierce... - She's the...
没错 我们正在...
Yeah, you know, we have a little thing...
-知道 没事 我听说了  -正在交往
- Yeah, yeah. Fine. I heard. - ...going.
会很尴尬吗 她...她和我处得还不错
It's not weird? She, she's kind of good for me.
-不 当然可以  -谢谢
- No, sure. Yeah. - Thank you.
-瞧瞧我们  -我知道
- Look at us, huh? Huh? - I know.
还有我看到了剃须刀 所以...
Also, I saw the razors, so...
-什么  -你浴室里的剃须刀
- What? - The razors in your bathroom?
-是谁的  -等等... 什么
- Whose are those? - Wait...wh...
你去我浴室干嘛
Why were you in my bathroom?
因为我不想在员工卫生间里解大手
Because I don't like to drop a deuce where the staff go.
好吧 天呐 肯 那并不代表...
Yeah. Oh, God. Ken, uh, those don't actually mean...
-不是吗 男士剃须刀欸  -什么... 当然不是
- Oh, no? Male razors? - What... no!
男士剃须刀更便宜些
Uh, they're less expensive.
所以你是说我没给你足够的赡养费
Oh, so I'm not giving you enough money
买女性用的剃须刀吗
for gender-appropriate razors now?
肯 我现在不想和你聊这个
Ken, I'm not having this conversation right now.
我说笑的 说笑的
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
-我不是来说这个的  -挺好笑的
- This isn't that conversation. - It's funny. Good.
-嗨 肯  -怎么了
- Hey, Ken. - Yeah?
丽莎和基思来了
Uh, Lisa and Keith are here.
-嗨 肯  -嗨 天才团队
- Hey, Ken. - Hey, hey, Team Genius!
-感谢你们特地赶来  -我的荣幸
- Thank you for coming. - My pleasure.
基思 我叫肯德尔 请坐
Keith, Kendall. Please sit.
你们要喝些什么吗
Uh, can I, can I get you anything?
-不 我不用了 谢谢  -不用  确定吗
- No, I'm good. Thank you. - You're good? You sure?
拉瓦 我们只要占用四五个小时
Rav, it'll just be four or five hours.
-好吧 没事  -看谁来了
- Uh, yeah, fine. - Okay, hey. Here she is.
-你好  -你好哇
- Hi. - Hello.
是什么风把您吹来了
Look what the Aegean dragged in.
对了 我正在... 我想给你介绍一下
Okay, I'm right in the middle... So, I want to introduce you.
这是拉瓦 拉瓦 这是内奥米
This is Rava. Rava, Naomi.
-你好  -你好
- Hey. - Hi.
很高兴见到你
So good to meet you.
还要谢谢你的慷慨
And thank you for this.
没什么 不用谢
Oh, yeah, no. Yeah, not at all.
我... 我得去...
I just gotta...I gotta...
-我也是 格雷格 你能帮帮...  -什么
- Me too. Hey, Greg, can you help, uh... - Yeah?
-招待内奥米吗 我得...  -哦 好的
- ...Naomi, I gotta... Yeah. - Oh, yeah.
也就是说...
So...
他还在欧洲 惊慌失措
He's still in Europe. He's scared.
我爸好像跑去了萨拉热窝
And it looks like my dad's gone to Sarajevo.
好吧 我先声明
Okay. So, I should, um, make it clear
现在只是初步的行动
this is just a preliminary.
所以不要透露机密信息
So, no confidential information.
了解 了解 我想想看能告诉你些什么
Sure. Sure. Well, look, what can I tell you?
我爸爸是个恶魔
Uh... my dad's the devil.
他经营着一个犯罪集团 我之所以想请你们
He runs a crime ring, and I would love to hire you
是因为你们是这方面的明星律师
because you're a super star
我觉得你们能扳倒我爸爸
and I think you can take down my dad,
而且这会是一件世纪诉讼案
and this will be the case of the century
-足以成就你们事业的高光时刻  -好吧
- and the highlight of your career. - Okay. Okay.
-这或许... -我是说真的 他们会拍一部关于你的电影
- Well, that might be... - I'm serious. They'll make a movie about you.
我们应该为你拍部电影
We should make a movie about you.
别人会怎么看呢
And how would that look?
他们会觉得超赞 因为会拍得很精彩
It would look amazing, because it would be brilliant!
好吧 听着 现在情况很复杂
Okay, look, this is quite a complex situation to progress
因为据我的理解 你想扳倒你爸爸
because, as I understand it, you want to take down your dad
-同时避免拉你自己下水  -没错
- without implicating yourself? - Correct.
也不会过分影响到公司
And without damaging the company to the extent
你就不会在股东大会上失去掌控权
that you lose control at your shareholder meeting?
-没错  -那你知道
- Correct. - And you know
小西和我是朋友关系
that Shiv and I have had a friend relationship?
知道 这总有办法解决的
Yeah, well, that might work out anyway.
好吧 这是你们俩要解决的 但首先
Okay, well, that's for you two, but first things.
政府目前是否联系过你
Has the government reached out to you yet?
或者你有没有收到相关文件的传票
Or have you received a subpoena for the documents yet?
不 没有 我先说清楚
No, no. And look, to be clear,
我会完全按你说的去做
I will do whatever you tell me to do.
我就是你的傀儡
I am your puppet.
好吧 那么首先 我们得确认
Okay. Well, in the first instance, we need to make sure
你和你在圣安德鲁的朋友完全没有牵扯
you're in the clear with your friends at one, Saint Andrew's.
-好的  -所以最先需要确保
- Right. - So, first thing is to make sure
你不会自投罗网  好吗 小傀儡
your head isn't on the block, okay, puppet?
丽莎 我觉得你就是我要找的律师
Lisa, I feel like you're my lawyer!
你他妈在干嘛 格雷格 你有什么毛病
Oh, for fuck's sake! Greg! What the fuck?
-我马上回来  -肯
- Be right back. - Ken!
-杰西 你能...  -好的
- Jess, can you... - Yep.
肯
Ken!
-我很抱歉  -来了 我来了
- I'm so sorry. - Yeah. I'm right here.
恕我爆粗 你难道没看到瓶子上全是灰吗
I'm sorry, did you not see that there was dust all over the bottle?
-没事吧  -你难道没想到...
- We okay? - Did you not think to...
-行 算了  -我真的不... 真的对不起 拉瓦
- No, it's fine. - I really had no... I'm really sorry, Rava.
-算了  -怎么了
- It is fine. - What?
这瓶酒是我教父送我的
That was one my godfather gave me.
内奥米让我打开的 肯
Naomi told me to open it, Ken.
所以我就...
And so I just...
-我很抱歉 拉瓦  -对不起
- Well, I'm very sorry, Rava. - I'm so sorry.
-格雷格 没关...  -嗨
- Greg, that's not... - Hi.
-你好  -你好哇 哎呀 抱歉
- Hey. - Hey, ooh, sorry.
不不不 各位 你们喝吧 请尽情享用
No, no, no. Guys, drink it, enjoy it.
-我真的不是针对你...  -没关系 没事
- I don't want any personally... - It's fine! It's good.
每当有人破坏了美丽的东西
It's like when someone breaks something beautiful
都在提醒你没有什么是天长地久的
and it reminds you that nothing lasts.
请享用吧
Enjoy it.
我去拿些纸巾
I'll get some napkins.
瞧瞧这些优秀的女性 格雷格
All these brilliant fucking women, Greg.
-我想说...  - 我总有什么事是做对的吧
- I mean... - Hey, I must be doing something right.
-是吧  -是的
- Right? Right? - You are.
你做的一切都是对的 先生
You're doing everything right, man.
你站在世界之巅
You are on top of the world.
好的 我很快回来
Okay. Uh, I'll be back in a flash.
好了 宝贝儿 丽莎·亚瑟 我现在是你一个人的了
All right, baby. Lisa Arthur, you got my undivided attention.
-小西呢  -我正在找她
- Where's Shiv? - I'm trying.
看来格丽担任总裁的消息走漏了
Looks like the Gerri CEO news might have leaked.
我让西蒙通知董事会待命
And I got Simon on the board lined up.
-你想要开个房间吗  -还用说 我他妈当然想要个房间
- Do you want a room? - Yes, I want a fucking room!
我马上要连着三个小时当孙子
I'm about to eat dick for three hours straight,
所以没错 雨果 我他妈想要开个房间
so, yes, Hugo, I would like a fucking room.
好吧
Okay.
肯德尔·罗伊
别再给我添堵了
I don't need that.
肯德尔
Kendall.
好的
Right.
当然 随便你吧
Sure, well, whatever.
-又怎么了  -没事 晚点再告诉你
- What now? - Nothing, tell you later.
-快他妈的说吧  -不是什么大事
- Go on, fucking say! - It's not a big deal.
丽莎·亚瑟要代理肯德尔
Lisa Arthur is going to represent Kendall.
行啊
Fine.
那我们去找莱欧
Let's get Layo.
我们要把他们生吞活剥
We'll fucking beast 'em.
全他妈给我下地狱
We'll go full fucking beast!